<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mackenzie Patel</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/</link><description>Recent content on Mackenzie Patel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://littlecurrywurst.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Quarter End Close: 60 Hours of Accounting in One Week</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/closeweek/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/closeweek/</guid><description>No need to worry, my accountant handles that
I usually don’t write about my secret life of accounting, but this past week was a professional and intellectual doozy. My normal work week is about 40 to 45 hours of meetings, esoteric accounting principles and analyzing reams of numbers on Excel. Once a quarter though, all hell breaks loose in the accounting department and 60-70 hours are spent per person on closing up the books for the 10-Q.</description></item><item><title>What To Do After Finishing Work for the Day Besides Watching Netflix</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/afterwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/afterwork/</guid><description>Your fingers have finally left the keyboard; your vehicle of intellectual destiny (your laptop) is wheezing a slow death to the “off” button and that ripe IPA in the fridge is hissing. Eight hours have gone by - or was it ten? - and the night is outstretched like a ruby carpet. You could do anything. You could boil homemade preserves, learn the lyrics to the Ukranian national anthem or run two blocks to the nearest gas station, buy some CBD and run back.</description></item><item><title>Coasting Through Zion National Forest by Bike</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/zion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/zion/</guid><description>Lower Emerald Trail in Zion National Park.
Labor Day 2020 was a watershed moment for me: it was my first company holiday since starting Honeywell in July (yay for being an accounting shill!). Before working, I didn’t fully appreciate the obligatory days off my school or part-time work gave me - I would spend these free hours studying or lying around eating peanut butter and pretzels and watching Gossip Girl.</description></item><item><title>From Meaty Minestrone to Colorful Fiesta Bowls: My Fave Recipes from the Spoon University Cookbook</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/spoon-cookbook/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/spoon-cookbook/</guid><description>Stepping out of my culinary comfort zone with easy and semi-fancy recipes.
It’s about fifteen years too late, but my childhood dream of becoming a chef is finally being realized - the twinkle is in my brown eye, my face is dusted in bleached flour and I toss the phrase “just eyeball it” around like it’s my most beloved cliché. I may be an amateur (I still smoke up my kitchen when I get overzealous with salmon), but my skills have leveled up during quarantine.</description></item><item><title>I’m Slowly (Anxiously) Learning How to Rollerblade as an Adult</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/rollerblading/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/rollerblading/</guid><description>Becoming a rollerblading disco girl one flailing fall at a time. Photo by Mike Matheny on Unsplash
It’s a weird confession, but I woke up one Saturday late-morning and was itching to rollerblade around like a bar of Dial soap was strapped to my feet. I’ve never been good with “rollie” activities like roller skating, longboarding, ice skating, etc. My hands drip sheets of sweat, my heart starts pounding and my mind shows lovely films of my brain matter splatting on a dirty sidewalk.</description></item><item><title>Four and a Quarter Hours on the Hawthorne Trail</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/hawthorne/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/hawthorne/</guid><description>Teeming Cyprus grove on the trail fringes
The Hawthorne Trail: the epic, serpentine rail-turned-trail that graces Gainesville’s backyard and offers a smooth 32 miles of uninterrupted earth and clarity. I first started biking the Hawthorne Trail when I acquired Luna, a mint-green Admiral Schwinn with sticky gears and a seat that resembled a tortoiseshell. I was never a serious biker before I bought Luna. I would hop on the odd beach cruiser at home and wind throughout my neighborhood like it was the suburban Tour-de-France.</description></item></channel></rss>