<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mackenzie Patel</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/</link><description>Recent content on Mackenzie Patel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://littlecurrywurst.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Crying in H Mart with the Diving Women of Jeju Island</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/jeju/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/jeju/</guid><description>An ode to the diving women of Jeju-do
I want to be a woman of regimen A bride in her home state A diving woman of Jeju-do I want it all
Thus are the opening lines of Diving Woman by Japanese Breakfast, a psychedelic soft rock band with Michelle Zauner on vocals and guitar. It’s been my go-to “bliss out” song for years, and a tune that strikes me even harder after reading Zauner’s memoir, Crying in H Mart.</description></item><item><title>she256 Book Club Guide to Blockchain Chicken Farm by Xiaowei Wang</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/blockchainchicken/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/blockchainchicken/</guid><description>**
Our latest read for the she256 book club was Blockchain Chicken Farm: And Other Stories of Tech in China&amp;rsquo;s Countryside by Xiaowei Wang, a PhD student at UC Berkeley. Traversing across provinces and technology, this book offered a glimpse into the life of a modern Chinese peasant. Instead of farming with traditional tools or confining business just to the Chinese market, these rural residents are adopting buzzword tech like AI and blockchain to reach an international market.</description></item><item><title>she256 Book Club Guide to Sacred Economics</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/sacredeconomics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/sacredeconomics/</guid><description>Still Life with a broken Glass, Willem Claesz. Heda, 1642
I recently had the chance to lead the book club for she256, a nonprofit dedicated to advancing women and minority interests in crypto. We kicked off our first meeting with Sacred Economics by Charles Eisenstein, a treatise spanning economics, self-help, monetary policy and spirituality. It was an unusual pick for crypto internet strangers but also so refreshing - I had an incredible time talking about random topics like universal income, commoditization of life, squirrel habits and more.</description></item><item><title>The Case of the Mangled Blue Heron and My Jarring Wake-up Call to Care about the Environment</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/heron/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/heron/</guid><description>A beautiful conclusion to a terrifying night
It was your average Easter Sunday - my sister baked a glazed ham, mom brought the fluffy sweet potatoes with a crackle of gingersnaps and I was two beers in by our third hallelujah. My tummy was swelling by dusk so I took a walk around my pool and started Radium Girls on Libby, hoping to stroll off the calories. On my tenth lap or so, this giant blue heron flew low to our lawn and landed in a flurry by the air conditioner.</description></item><item><title>The Tragedy of My Medial Sesamoid Foot Bone</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/sesamoid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/sesamoid/</guid><description>Who knew feet could be so fragile?
I never thought I’d be writing an article about my physical deficiencies, especially when I’m a 23-year-old with enough internal energy to light up the federal power grid. However, the past few months have forced me to examine who I thought I was as I battled an injury I sustained nearly two years ago - and didn’t know it. This is the story of how I fractured my medial sesamoid bone in my left foot; it’s a tiny knob, barely perceptible since it’s tucked inside a tendon.</description></item><item><title>Getting into Crypto as a Technical N00b</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/crypto/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/crypto/</guid><description>All aboard the crypto gravy train
We all felt the heart palpitations as Bitcoin reached unparalleled heights during the holiday season, from ~$20,000 a BTC to a whopping ~$40,000 in the new year. Cryptocurrencies, especially Bitcoin, are infamous for their drunken swings and depression lows, causing dilettantes to either invest like hungry sailors or jump ship like the blockchain is aflame. Before Bitcoin gave us a hope of a trustless, decentralized financial system actually coming to fruition, I started studying cryptocurrencies and the underlying blockchain technology in October 2020.</description></item><item><title>I Didn't Expect a Chakra Journal by 'Amy &amp; Chad' to be this Insightful</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/chakras/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/chakras/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t judge a chakra book by its Western authors :}
2020 was the year of organic, “off brand” spirituality for me. I’ve been disillusioned with traditional religion since I left Lutheran (not Catholic😤) school in 7th grade, but in recent months, the lure of general spirituality has been strong. The pandemic and family problems wrecked my mental health and creative drive, but after reading books like The Untethered Soul, The Surrender Experiment and Many Lives, Many Masters, a small seed of “self” has been taking root again.</description></item><item><title>A Review of Impala Inline Rollerblades: Gliding into the 70s</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/impala/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/impala/</guid><description>The most beautiful shoes I own
Lacing up my pastel blue rollerblades is like slipping into a sparkly 70s daydream. The sunlight is simmering brown shoulders and thighs are the size of slick logs, pushing hard and sweating to propel yourself along the Santa Monica boardwalk. Ice cream drips, men sip on their summer shandys and finger their frayed beach towels. “It’s a perfect day for bananafish,” says J.</description></item><item><title>Pre Jam Papers (Part II)</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/jamtwo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/jamtwo/</guid><description>Jam filled donuts; the possibilities are endless!
Note: if you haven’t read Pre Jam Papers (Part I), you can check it out here - I recommend reading it beforehand so you have a solid foundation in canning methodologies and the overall preserving environment.
Welcome to my mischievous foray into learning to can my own pectin-loaded fruits! Hobbies have a history of whisking me away to the kitchen, Ancient Roman palaces and Long Beach sidewalks, and canning preserves is no different.</description></item><item><title>A Halcyon Day in San Francisco in Late October</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/sf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/sf/</guid><description>The Golden City, literally
It’s rare to have an authentic, enjoyable day from breakfast until midnight snack - something always pops up to confuse or tense the hours between opening your eyelids and shutting the lights off. But on October 16, 2020, I took my first official vacation day from the corporate wheel and lazed around the Golden City until sunset. It was a halcyon Friday that began with a frothy cappuccino and ended with a nighttime park crawl.</description></item><item><title>Pre Jam Papers (Part I)</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/prejampapers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/prejampapers/</guid><description>A manifesto about chunky jam
For some peculiar reason, I’ve decided that canning jam is the next side hustle I have to capitalize on. Meaty pieces of fruit wrapped in a warm blanket of gel really get me going, especially when there’s a piece of whole grain toast involved. My first exposure to preserves was at Pearl’s Barbecue, a gas station restaurant in Micanopy, FL - it’s as “old Florida” as you can get, and their homemade jams ranged from Dutch Apple and Peach to Spiced Apricot.</description></item><item><title>What Started out as a 72 Hour Fast Quickly Slid into 24 Hours of Yacc Macc</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/fasting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/fasting/</guid><description>Fasting with the boys
With the juiciest of intentions, I suggested to my boyfriend and his roommates that we all participate in a communal 72-hour fast. No calories, no carbs, no diet sodas that hide behind lobbying and advertising that claim Coke Zero is “good for you”. Just water (and black coffee and tea, if no creamers are added). I was jazzed for this fast because I’ve never gone a full day without eating before - it’s the pinnacle of living in the first world, as is writing this blog post on a mac laptop and wearing a Zara sweater knitted in Turkey.</description></item><item><title>Macc Takes On Grimy Outdoor Tent Camping</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/camping/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/camping/</guid><description>Campy Mack in her natural habitat
I skipped the outdoorsy camping phase in college (tent who?), but I’m more than making up for it as a confused adult. Living in Arizona has definitely induced this back-to-nature attitude and sprint to anything smelling like dirt and unmown weeds. Camping in the wilds with only a Coleman tent and dad’s flashlight is a far cry from the “glamping” I used to do - that usually involved foam mattresses, cabins, mess halls with vending machines and a working sink to wash my eyebrows in.</description></item><item><title>Quarter End Close: 60 Hours of Accounting in One Week</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/closeweek/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/closeweek/</guid><description>No need to worry, my accountant handles that
I usually don’t write about my secret life of accounting, but this past week was a professional and intellectual doozy. My normal work week is about 40 to 45 hours of meetings, esoteric accounting principles and analyzing reams of numbers on Excel. Once a quarter though, all hell breaks loose in the accounting department and 60-70 hours are spent per person on closing up the books for the 10-Q.</description></item><item><title>What To Do After Finishing Work for the Day Besides Watching Netflix</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/afterwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/afterwork/</guid><description>Your fingers have finally left the keyboard; your vehicle of intellectual destiny (your laptop) is wheezing a slow death to the “off” button and that ripe IPA in the fridge is hissing. Eight hours have gone by - or was it ten? - and the night is outstretched like a ruby carpet. You could do anything. You could boil homemade preserves, learn the lyrics to the Ukranian national anthem or run two blocks to the nearest gas station, buy some CBD and run back.</description></item><item><title>Coasting Through Zion National Forest by Bike</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/zion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/zion/</guid><description>Lower Emerald Trail in Zion National Park.
Labor Day 2020 was a watershed moment for me: it was my first company holiday since starting Honeywell in July (yay for being an accounting shill!). Before working, I didn’t fully appreciate the obligatory days off my school or part-time work gave me - I would spend these free hours studying or lying around eating peanut butter and pretzels and watching Gossip Girl.</description></item><item><title>From Meaty Minestrone to Colorful Fiesta Bowls: My Fave Recipes from the Spoon University Cookbook</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/spoon-cookbook/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/spoon-cookbook/</guid><description>Stepping out of my culinary comfort zone with easy and semi-fancy recipes.
It’s about fifteen years too late, but my childhood dream of becoming a chef is finally being realized - the twinkle is in my brown eye, my face is dusted in bleached flour and I toss the phrase “just eyeball it” around like it’s my most beloved cliché. I may be an amateur (I still smoke up my kitchen when I get overzealous with salmon), but my skills have leveled up during quarantine.</description></item><item><title>I’m Slowly (Anxiously) Learning How to Rollerblade as an Adult</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/rollerblading/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/rollerblading/</guid><description>Becoming a rollerblading disco girl one flailing fall at a time. Photo by Mike Matheny on Unsplash
It’s a weird confession, but I woke up one Saturday late-morning and was itching to rollerblade around like a bar of Dial soap was strapped to my feet. I’ve never been good with “rollie” activities like roller skating, longboarding, ice skating, etc. My hands drip sheets of sweat, my heart starts pounding and my mind shows lovely films of my brain matter splatting on a dirty sidewalk.</description></item><item><title>Four and a Quarter Hours on the Hawthorne Trail</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/hawthorne/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/hawthorne/</guid><description>Teeming Cyprus grove on the trail fringes
The Hawthorne Trail: the epic, serpentine rail-turned-trail that graces Gainesville’s backyard and offers a smooth 32 miles of uninterrupted earth and clarity. I first started biking the Hawthorne Trail when I acquired Luna, a mint-green Admiral Schwinn with sticky gears and a seat that resembled a tortoiseshell. I was never a serious biker before I bought Luna. I would hop on the odd beach cruiser at home and wind throughout my neighborhood like it was the suburban Tour-de-France.</description></item></channel></rss>