<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gainesville on Mackenzie Patel</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/tags/gainesville/</link><description>Recent content in Gainesville on Mackenzie Patel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://littlecurrywurst.com/tags/gainesville/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pre Jam Papers (Part II)</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/jamtwo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/jamtwo/</guid><description>Jam filled donuts; the possibilities are endless!
Note: if you haven’t read Pre Jam Papers (Part I), you can check it out here - I recommend reading it beforehand so you have a solid foundation in canning methodologies and the overall preserving environment.
Welcome to my mischievous foray into learning to can my own pectin-loaded fruits! Hobbies have a history of whisking me away to the kitchen, Ancient Roman palaces and Long Beach sidewalks, and canning preserves is no different.</description></item><item><title>Four and a Quarter Hours on the Hawthorne Trail</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/hawthorne/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/hawthorne/</guid><description>Teeming Cyprus grove on the trail fringes
The Hawthorne Trail: the epic, serpentine rail-turned-trail that graces Gainesville’s backyard and offers a smooth 32 miles of uninterrupted earth and clarity. I first started biking the Hawthorne Trail when I acquired Luna, a mint-green Admiral Schwinn with sticky gears and a seat that resembled a tortoiseshell. I was never a serious biker before I bought Luna. I would hop on the odd beach cruiser at home and wind throughout my neighborhood like it was the suburban Tour-de-France.</description></item></channel></rss>