<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spirituality on Mackenzie Patel</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/tags/spirituality/</link><description>Recent content in Spirituality on Mackenzie Patel</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://littlecurrywurst.com/tags/spirituality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>she256 Book Club Guide to Sacred Economics</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/sacredeconomics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/sacredeconomics/</guid><description>Still Life with a broken Glass, Willem Claesz. Heda, 1642
I recently had the chance to lead the book club for she256, a nonprofit dedicated to advancing women and minority interests in crypto. We kicked off our first meeting with Sacred Economics by Charles Eisenstein, a treatise spanning economics, self-help, monetary policy and spirituality. It was an unusual pick for crypto internet strangers but also so refreshing - I had an incredible time talking about random topics like universal income, commoditization of life, squirrel habits and more.</description></item><item><title>I Didn't Expect a Chakra Journal by 'Amy &amp; Chad' to be this Insightful</title><link>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/chakras/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://littlecurrywurst.com/blog/chakras/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t judge a chakra book by its Western authors :}
2020 was the year of organic, “off brand” spirituality for me. I’ve been disillusioned with traditional religion since I left Lutheran (not Catholic😤) school in 7th grade, but in recent months, the lure of general spirituality has been strong. The pandemic and family problems wrecked my mental health and creative drive, but after reading books like The Untethered Soul, The Surrender Experiment and Many Lives, Many Masters, a small seed of “self” has been taking root again.</description></item></channel></rss>